Guide to the Japanese-American Relocation Centers records, 1935-1953.
Japanese-American Relocation Centers records,
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Japanese American relocation centers records, 1935-1953
3830
22.9 cubic ft.
Reports, studies, autobiographies, blueprints, interviews, paintings, poems, yearbooks, newsclippings.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Includes documentation collected by military sociologists on two World War II-era Japanese-American relocation centers, along with sociological observations and studies.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
The documentation comprising the Japanese-American Relocation Centers Records was primarily collected by Lt. Alexander Leighton and Morris Opler. Leighton, a sociologist in the Naval Reserve, assembled extensive records on life in the Poston Center for use in studying the psychological and social effects of dislocation. Drawing on his research, he wrote The Governing of Men: General Principles and Recommendations Based on Experience at a Japanese Relocation Camp (Princeton, N.J.: Princeton University Press, 1945). Opler, a sociologist for the War Relocation Authority (WRA) Community Analysis Section, collected the less extensive Manzanar Center records. Together the records provide details about life in Poston and Manzanar from 1942 through 1944. Because the collection was assembled by social scientists, the documents also afford an opportunity to examine social science concerns and methodology during the 1940s.
Poston Relocation Center records consist of National Opinion Research Center (NORC) and Poston Opinion Research Center (PORC) reports, autobiographies, observations, observer analyses, personality studies, transcripts of interviews, and other data documenting community government, education, employment, entertainment, food, health, housing, religion, social welfare, and camp organizations in Poston. Also included are WRA memoranda, camp administrative instructions, and administrators' and evacuees' notes and observations on various aspects of camp life, including evacuation and relocation. Many of the records analyze the interns' day-to-day experiences as well as unusual occurrences such as a labor strike at Poston. There are numerous documents of a more personal nature, such as watercolor paintings by camp residents, depicting scenes of camp life and its landscape. In addition there are Japanese-American newspapers, camp newspapers, and pamphlets further describing life at the Poston Relocation Center. There is also an extensive clipping file on Japanese-American relocation and full issues of the Poston Chronicle, an organization chart of Poston, a boundary map and blueprint of Manzanar, a scrapbook, yearbooks, and 137 watercolors, painted by Gene Sogioka.
Statistical analyses and charts accompany many of the series within the collection.
ABBREVIATIONS USED
WRA
War Relocation Authority
BSR
Bureau of Sociological Research
NORC
National Opinion Research Center
PORC
Poston Opinion Research Center
TCC
Temporary Community Council
IAB
Issei Advisory Board
AHL
Alexander H. Leighton
YWCA
Young Women's Christian Association
HUAC
House Un-American Activities Committee
CEB
Central Executive Board
EHS
E. H. Spicer
MEO
Morris E. Opler
JACL
Japanese American Citizens' League
OTHER CAMPS AND LOCATIONS
Gila River, Arizona
Granada, Colorado
Heart Mountain, Wyoming
Jenson, Arkansas
Jerome, Arkansas
Minidoka, Idaho
Rohwer, Arkansas
Topaz, Utah
Tule Lake, California
SUBJECTS
Names:
Sogioka, Gene.; Leighton, Alexander H. (Alexander Hamilton), 1908-; Opler, Morris Edward, 1907-; Manzanar War Relocation Center.; National Opinion Research Center.; Poston Opinion Research Center.; Poston Relocation Center (Poston, Ariz.); United States. War Relocation Authority.
Subjects:
Concentration camps--United States.; Japanese Americans--Evacuation and relocation, 1942-1945.; World War, 1939-1945--Evacuation of civilians.
Form and Genre Terms:
Autobiographies.; Blueprints.; Interviews.; Paintings.; Poems.; Yearbooks.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Access to Boxes 26-29 (artwork) and Box 30 (medical records) restricted to the permission of the curator.
Available Copies:
Some watercolors are reproduced in: Deborah Gesensway and Mindy Roseman, Beyond words: images from America's concentration camps (Ithaca, N.Y.: Cornell University Press, 1987). (P. 85 - #92, p. 106 - #29, p. 115 - #5, p. 138 - #3, p. 148 - #133, p. 149 - #15, p. 150 - #116, p. 151 - #122, p.152 - #32, p.153 - #4, p. 155 - #126)
SERIES LIST
Series I. Poston
National Administration
Box 1
Bureau of Sociological Research
Boxes 2-4
City management
Boxes 4-6
Community government
Boxes 6-7
Block studies
Box 7
Statistics
Box 7
Census reports
Boxes 7-8
Community enterprises
Box 8
Associations
Box 8
Health
Box 8
Education
Boxes 8-9
Subsistence
Box 9
Work projects
Box 9
Employment
Box 10
Social welfare
Box 10
Religion
Box 10
Evacuation, evacuee property
Box 10
Segregation
Box 11
Selective Service
Box 11
Outgroup relations
Box 11
Personality studies (restricted until August 26, 2003)
Boxes 11-12
Sociological journal, newspapers
Box 13
Bibliography
Box 13
Miscellaneous Poston materials
Box 13, 38
Manuscript notes--Leighton, "Governing of Man"
Box 13
Miscellaneous oversized materials
Boxes 22, 27, 33
Series II. Manzanar
State Department
Box 15
Post War World Council
Box 15
Congressional Records
Box 15
Tolan Committee
Box 15
Dies Committee
Box 15
House UnAmerican Activities Commission
Box 15
National Defense Migration
Box
WRA National Administration
Box 15, 16
Community Government
Box 16
Community Analysis Section
Box 16
Project Reports
Box 16
Information Center Daily Reports
Box 16, 17
Town Hall Daily Reports
Box 17
Block Leaders' Council
Box 17
Block Managers Assembly
Box 17
Historical Documentation
Box 17
History of Internal Government at Manzanar
Box 17
General Information
Box 17
Education
Box 17
Medical and Health Survey
Box 17
Manzanar Miscellaneous Reports
Box 17
Welfare Hearings
Box 17, 18
Leave Clearance General Cases and Outlines
Box 18
Relocation
Box 18, 19
Segregation
Box 19
Repatriation
Box 19
Miscellaneous
Box 19
Clipping file
Boxes 19-24, 38
Series III. Oversized material
Miscellaneous
Boxes 25-29
Watercolors
Boxes 26-29
Miscellaneous
Boxes 19, 28, 31-37, Mapcase
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Poston
  - National administration
    - Meeting on the background of the Japanese, evacuee poems, WRA background reports. (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Office of Indian Affairs and WRA relations and administration- discussion, speech by Indian Affairs commissioner, letters about personnel. (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - WRA Information Digests Jan 2, 1943-Oct. 15, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - WRA general policies including personnel, administration, memos, speeches, Japanese customs, background. (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - WRA general policies including camp gov't., regulations, reports, administrators, reports on registration. (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - WRA quarterly reports- March-June 1942, July-Sept. 1942, WRA Relocation Program report in Japanese. (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - WRA Leighton-Myer correspondence and reports on issue of stepped-up resettlement program. (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - WRA administrative instructions May 30-Aug. 12, 1942. (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - WRA administrative instructions Aug. 17-25, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - WRA administrative instructions Sept. 1-30, 1942. (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - WRA administrative instructions Oct. 1-29, 1942. (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - WRA administrative instructions Nov. 3-Dec. 26, 1942. (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - WRA administrative instructions Jan. 1-29, 1943. (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - WRA administrative instructions Feb. 1943. (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - WRA administrative instructions March 1943. (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - WRA administrative instructions April 1943. (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - WRA administrative instructions May 1943. (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - WRA administrative instructiuons June-July 1943 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - WRA administrative instructions Aug.-Oct. 1943. (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - WRA Daily Press Reviews from San Francisco Regional Office, Sept. 2-Dec. 11, 1942. (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - WRA Weekly Press Review Jan. 18-Apr. 28, 1943. (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - WRA Weekly Press Review May 5-Sept. 29, 1943. (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - WRA Weekly Press Review Jan. 12-Mar. 29, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - WRA Weekly Press Review Apr. 5-June 21, 1944. (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - WRA Weekly Press Review June 28-Sept. 6, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - WRA Community Analysis Section Project Analyses Series #1-14, Feb. 1943-March 1944, Topics: Registration at Central Utah Army Registration at Granada Registration at Manzanar The Fence and Watchtowers Preliminary Evaluation of the Resettlement Program at Jerome Relocation Center Report on an Unorganized Relocation Center Notes on some religious cults at Topaz Factors Influencing Low Enrollment in Certain Adult Education Courses Preliminary Survey of Resistances to Resettlement at the Tule Lake Relocation Center Japanese-English language Notes on Evacuee Family Patterns Studies of Segregants at Manzanar Boilermen's Dispute at Minidoka Tule Lake Incident (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - WRA Community Analysis Section Project Analyses Series #16-24, April 1944-Feb.1946., Topics: Significant factors in requests for repatriation and expatriation Relocation at Rohwer Center Community Government in the Relocation Centers A typical Block at Tule Lake Center Gila River Relocation Center Stresses and Strains of Center Life (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - WRA Community Analysis Section Reports Feb. 1943-Nov. 1945, Topics: Causes of Unrest at Relocation Centers Japanese Groups and Associations in the U.S. Notes on Japanese Holidays Nisei Assimilation An analysis of the Segregation Program The Kibei Buddhism in the U.S. Labor relations in the relocation Centers Survey of (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - WRA Community Analysis Section Reports Feb.-June 1946, Topics: Annotated Bibliographies (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Community Analysis Section, Granada Report #2-Evacuee Attitudes on Relocation (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Community Analysis Section Notes Jan. 15, 1944-Apr. 16, 1945, Topics: From a Nisei Who said "No" Engagement and Marriage Customs in a Relocation Center Traditional Japanese Therapeutics practiced at Minidoka Social and Political Organization of the Block at Manzanar A Nisei Requests Repatriation Biography of a Nisei Celery Farmer from Venice, California Nisei Report on their adjustment to Tule Lake West Coast localities: San Joaquin County (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Community Analysis Section, Letters, Apr. 19, 1943-Nov. 3, 1944, and Administrative Instructions (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Community Analysis Section, Miscellaneous studies, newspaper clippings, minutes of meetings, field reports from other centers, correspondence between Leighton and Sweetser (CAS in Washington) July-Aug. 1943 about Poston, Report, miscellaneous correspondence, Bibliography on WRA, Japanese and Jap-Ams Oct.-July 1943. (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Bureau of Sociological Research
    - Administrative Records of BSR, contracts (charter from Dept. of Interior to Leighton), for Research Bureau. (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Administrative Records of BSR budgets ( 1943 ) (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Administrative Records of BSR library material- correspondence with libraries for reference material, overdue notices, etc. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Administrative Records of BSR personnel bi-monthly repts. (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Administrative Records of BSR personnel and applications (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Administrative Records of BSR purchase requests. (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Administrative Records of BSR purchase requests continued. (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Administrative Records of BSR Leighton travel vouchers ( 1943-44 ) and travel tickets (envelope). (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Administrative Records of BSR receipts for Government Quarters and meals. (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Administrative records of BSR miscellaneous letters and notes. (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - History of Poston I ( May-Dec. 1942 ), 2 drafts and comments of "We came to the beginning of the Year." (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Staff meetings and cross reference topics- Aug. 1942, preliminary meeting (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Staff meeting- Sept. 1942 - topics include: Food, housing, cultural background, policy (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Staff meeting- Oct. 1942 - topics include: Political situation in Poston II, agriculture, report to Anthro. Society, Overall program (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Staff meeting- Nov. 1942 - topics include: Methodology, cliques and class, chronology of meetings and field techniques. (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Staff meeting- Dec. 1942 - topics include: review of events, food, Poston strike, book review. (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Staff Meeting- Jan. 1943 - topics include: co-op movement in Poston, review, analysis of questionnaire of evacuees about outide conditions, Chippewa Indians, Buddhism, Jerome relocation center. (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Staff Meeting- Feb. 1943 - topics include: public opinion, Methodology, Buddhist assoc., Influences of other relocation centers on Poston, work projects. (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Staff Meeting-- Feb. 1943 - topics include: Housing, food, misc., health, history of Poston, co-ops and community industry, outgroup relations, self-government in Poston. (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Staff Meeting- Feb. 1943 - Topics include: Pre-school and school system, administration and staff meetings, plans for filing system, personality studies. (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Staff Meeting- March 1943 - topics include: History of Poston, misc., Camp III report, books. (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Staff Meeting- April 1943 - topics include: Administrative misc., NORC, Minidoka and Poston strike, census and statistics, PORC, International history day. (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Staff Meeting- May 1943 - topics include: business, Planning an administration with resident participation, Misc., national history, education, history, Jap-Am in U.S. (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Staff Meeting- June 1943 - topics include: Minidoka, elections, misc. weekly events, survey on methodology, camp history. (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Staff Meeting- July, Aug. 1943 - topics include: local history, research, profile of block 26, book outline, general business. (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Staff Meeting- Sept., Oct. 1943 - in Chicago- topics include: general business, sentiments. (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Staffs and policies- contain personality studies, drafts, flowcharts, misc. speeches, requests. (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - AHL monthly reports on Poston to Admiral McIntire (US Navy), correspondence Nov. 1942-May 1943 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Articles by Bureau of Sociological Research, correspondence (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Weekly summaries of community events Oct. 1942-Aug. 1943. (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Weekly summaries of departmental events. (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Weekly summaries, original drafts (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Weekly summaries of weekly events by A.H. Leehs (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - NORC correspondence, surveys, results (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - NORC confidential reports anc charts (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - NORC publications (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - NORC press releases Dec. 6, 1942-April 1944 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - NORC drafts of articles on "resettlement" for Public Opinion Quarterly. (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - PORC research and documentation, notes on other sources, notes on questionnaires, notes on interview experiences, weekly news summaries, community meetings, notes and personal journals (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - PORC specifications, instructions, interviewers meetings, misc. (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - PORC Denver notes and correspondence for J-1 survey, personal journals, interview experiences, correspondence with Flo. (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - PORC notes taken by Vatsushiro and Ishiro during J-1, list of people interviewed, report of J-1. (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - PORC survey J-1 (Denver: Jap-American attitudes), report, commentary and tally sheets, final report. (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - PORC J-1 completed interviews. (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - PORC survey J-2 (resettlement of Nisei at Poston) tabulated results of survey, breakdown of statistics, statistical analysis and question analysis, stability charts, misc. notes and statistics, final report. (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - PORC J-2 completed interviews (No to quest. #1) (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - PORC J-2 completed interviews (Yes to quest. #1)) (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - PORC survey J-3, (resettlement of Issei at Poston) final report, list of interviewers, block managers list, synopsis of interviews, letters, specifications, statistics, guidelines, worship opinion survey agenda, minutes of meetings. (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - PORC J-3 statistics, block quota sheets, Poston census information (Population info.), stability charts and statistics, question analysis. (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - PORC J-3 completed interviews (Yes and o.k. to quest. #1) (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - PORC J-3 completed interviews (No to quest. #1) (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - PORC J-4, J-5 (Ag. Survey) includes letters, minutes of block managers meetings, minutes of Ag. Meetings, question for J-4, Final reports and notes. (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - PORC J-4, J-5 statistics (tabulated results), question analysis and comments. (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - PORC J-4 completed interviews (1-150) (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - PORC J-4 completed interviews (151-230) (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - PORC J-5 completed interviews (1-100) (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - PORC J-5 completed interviews (101-218) (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - PORC J-5 untranslated completed interviews (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - PORC age survey and other vital statistics about Poston. (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - PORC public relations (reports of PORC work) (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - PORC rumors about camp life, other events gathered in the community Sept. 1942, Mar.-June 1943 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - PORC sentiments- definition, camp events, daily life, charts. (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - PORC weekly evaluation and charts ( April - August ), explanation of chronology graphs, satisfaction ratings. (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - PORC weekly sentiment analysis, sentiment charts, community sentiment, cross references with other series: Religion, recreation, health, shelter, subsistence, social relations, statistical analysis. Covers period from July 5-Oct. 17, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - PORC weekly sentiment analysis covers weeks from Nov. 8-Dec. 12, 1942. (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - PORC weekly sentiment analysis covers weeks from Jan. 3, 1942-June 12, 1943, misc. notes on sentiment, outline for sentiment study. (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Chicago courses, includes correspondence with University of Chicago July 1942-June 1943, course description, reports to registrar, transcripts of research workers and psychobio exams (mid term and finals). (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - City management
    - City Management- topics include: general information, organization, departments, interviews concerning various functions of city management, 1943. (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Block Manager System- policies, instructions, organization, requests, memos (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Block Manager System- personnel appointments and resignations (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Block Manager System- merit rating board, study of Block Manager system staff and conclusions. (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Block Manager Systen- Executive committee meetings, minutes Sept. 7, 1942-July 22, 1943. (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Block Manager System- Meetings for Poston I, May 20-July 31, 1942. (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Block Manager System- Meeting minutes Poston I, Aug. 3-Oct. 30, 1942. (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Block Manager System- Meeting minutes Poston I, Nov. 3, 1942-Mar. 16, 1943 and July 27, 1943. (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Block Manager System- Meeting minutes Poston II, July 9-Aug. 25, 1942. (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Block Manager System- Meeting minutes Poston III, Aug. 11-Sept. 22, 1942. (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Block Manager System- Meeting minutes Poston III, Sept. 22-Dec. 15, 1942. (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Block Manager's Meeting minutes Poston III, Dec. 18, 1942-Aug. 20 1943. (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Block Manager's Logs- Block #2 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Block Manager's Logs- Block #3 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Block Manager's Logs- Block #4 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Block Manager's Logs- Block #5 Sept. 1-Oct. 30 1942 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Block Manager's Logs- Block #6 Sept. 1, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Block Manager's Logs- Block #11 Sept. 1, 1943, July 3-17, 1943. (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Block Manager's Logs- Block #12 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Block Manager's Logs- Block # 13 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Block Manager's Logs- Block #14 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Block Manager's Logs- Block #15 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Block Manager's Logs- Block #16 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Block Manager's Logs- Block #17 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Block Manager's Logs- Block #18 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Block Manager's Logs- Block #19, Sept. 1, 1942-Jan. 6, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Block Manager's Logs- Block #19 (continued) Jan. 7-May 31, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Block Manager's Logs- Block #21 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Block Manager's Logs- Block # 22 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Block Manager's Logs- Block #26 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Block Manager's Logs- Block #27, Sept. 1-Oct. 20, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Block Manager's Logs- Block # 28, Sept. 1, 1942-May 1, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Block Manager's Logs- Block # 30, Sept. 12, 1942-Jan. 23, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Block Manager's Logs- Block #31 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Block Manager's Logs- Block #32 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Block Manager's Logs- Block #35, Aug. 28, 1942-Dec. 31, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Block Manager's Logs- Block #35 (continued) Jan. 1-Apr. 15, 1943 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Block Manager's Logs- Block #35 (continued) Apr. 16-July 23, 1943 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Block Manager's Logs- Block #36 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Block Manager's Logs- Block #37 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Block Manager's Logs- Block #38 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Block Manager's Logs- Block #39, Sept. 1, 1942-Jan. 6, 1943 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Block Manager's Logs- Block #42 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Block Manager's Logs- Block #43 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Block Manager's Logs- Block #44 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Block Manager's Logs- Block #45, Aug. 18, 1942-Apr. 19, 1943 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Block Manager's Logs- Block #46, Aug. 27, 1942-May 5, 1943 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Block Manager's Logs- Block #53 Sept.-Nov. 1942 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Block Manager's Logs- Block #53 (continued) Dec. 1942-May 1943 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Block Manager's Logs- Block #54 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Block Manager's Logs- Block #59 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Block Manager's Logs- Block #60 May 14, 1943 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Block Manager's Logs- Block #306 Sept. 28, 1942-June 26, 1943 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Block Manager's Logs- Block #307 Sept. 28, 1942-July 3, 1943 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Block Manager's Logs- Block #308 Sept. 28, 1942-July 1943 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Block Manager's Logs- Block #309 Sept. 1942-July 1943 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Block Manager's Logs- Block #310 Sept. 15, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Block Manager's Logs- Block #316 Sept. 1942-July 1943 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Block Manager's Logs- Block #317 Sept. 1942-July 1943 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Block Manager's Logs- Block #318 Sept. 1942-June 1943 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Block Manager's Logs- Block #322 Sept. 1942-May 1943 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Block Manager's Logs- Block #323 Oct. 1942-July 1943 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Block Manager's Logs- Block #325 Sept. 1942-July 1943 (Box 5, Folder 27)